

PROFILE

Worked at Cloudlogic wherein we provide responsive e-commerce website to our top brands client here in the Philippines.

Intern at Pierre and Paul Solutions Inc. and Created some applications using Laravel Framework that they are currently using such as PPSI Employee Locator System, Inventory System

A Civil Service Passer – March 26, 2023

CONTACT

PHONE: 0929-522-5777

WEBSITE PORTFOLIO LINK:

https://jndelacruz0420.github.io/jnbdc portfolio/

EMAIL:

delacruzjohnnoel0922@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Playing online games Watching movies Travel

JOHN NOEL B. DELA CRUZ

Web Developer

EDUCATION

San Juan National High School

2008 - 2012

P. Narciso St. Brgy. Corazon De Jesus San Juan City

Polytechnic University of the Philippines

2012 - 2014, 2017 - 2020

Bachelor of Science Information Technology (Graduate)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pierre and Paul Solutions Inc.

Software Developer (Intern) Dec 2018 – March 2019

- Developed useful office software application using Laravel 5
- Developed PPSI Empcator and Accounting system

Cloudlogic Inc.

Web Developer Apr 2019 – July 2023

- Developed top brands E-commerce website in the Philippines with responsive design
- Contributed to back-end experience and collaborated on APIs.

SKILLS

- MySQL
- Google Analytics
- iQuery
- Project management
- CSS
- JavaScript
- HTML
- Ajax
- MVC Frameworks